https://shop.ei-oasis.com/ei-oasis/outpost/privacy

Create an Account
Hello, Guest!
Go
$0.00 (0 items)
Ink & Toner
Search by printer manufacturer or model number:
Returning Customer
Email:
Password:
Log In
Forgot Password?
Environmental Innovations, Inc.
Privacy Policy
We take your privacy very seriously.
Please review the following list to familiarize yourself with our policies and practices.
You are encouraged to review this policy regularly, as it may be changed without notification.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
We may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. Our data encryption ensures your information is protected before it is sent to the Internet. Our encryption process makes doing business over the Internet as secure as purchasing by telephone.
Our technology uses 128-bit encryption Secure Sockets (SSL) software for secure online transactions. You can identify a secure page by noticing the lock or key icon in the bottom right corner of your browser window. In addition, a secure web site address will display as "https" rather than just "http."
Don't Sell My Data
.
Copyright © 2020, ECI Software Solutions, Inc. All rights reserved.
